[{"question": " all right!  yes!! from home to the hospital in under seven minutes! we did it!!", "answer": "  yes, the hard part is truly over.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 1, "asentId": 2}, {"question": " oh you made it!", "answer": " hi!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 5, "asentId": 6}, {"question": " how are you doing?", "answer": " wait a minute! how-how the hell did you beat us here?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 7, "asentId": 8}, {"question": " we took a cab. did you guys walk?", "answer": " n&#133; no! we took a cab too, but i did test runs!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 9, "asentId": 10}, {"question": " hi!", "answer": " hey! you made it!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 11, "asentId": 12}, {"question": " okay is there&#133;some kind of magic tunnel to this hospital?!", "answer": " ross, you stay here and talk, i&#146;m gonna go have a baby.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 13, "asentId": 14}, {"question": " okay. okay.  umm hi, this is rachel green. i&#146;m ross geller. we-we called from the car.", "answer": " right! we have a semi-private labor room waiting for you. so in just a minute&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 15, "asentId": 16}, {"question": "  whoa-whoa-whoa-whoa! i&#146;m sorry, semi-private? we , we asked for a private room.", "answer": " yes, i see that here. unfortunately we can&#146;t guarantee a private room and currently they&#146;re all unavailable.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 17, "asentId": 18}, {"question": " i&#146;m sorry. semi-private rooms are all we have.", "answer": " okay. just give us a second. ross!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 21, "asentId": 22}, {"question": " yeah?", "answer": " give her some money.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 23, "asentId": 24}, {"question": " i really think they&#146;re out of rooms.", "answer": " they&#146;re not!! ross, they&#146;re just saving them for the important people!! okay?! what-what if i was the president?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 25, "asentId": 26}, {"question": " well then we&#146;d be in a lot of trouble, you don&#146;t know where any countries are.  okay.  uh, say would you umm&#133; would you mind checking again to see if any umm, private rooms may have  opened up?", "answer": " this is a hospital.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 27, "asentId": 28}, {"question": "  okay. y&#146;know what? i&#146;d have to say i really don&#146;t care for your tone. and this is not the only hospital in this city and we have no problem to&#151;whoa!  oh gosh! whoa!", "answer": " what-what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 29, "asentId": 30}, {"question": " would you like to see a semi-private room?", "answer": " yeah, it couldn&#146;t hurt to look.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 33, "asentId": 34}, {"question": " well you&#146;re only two centimeters dilated and we need to get to ten. it&#146;ll be a while.", "answer": " oh, okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 35, "asentId": 36}, {"question": " i&#146;ll be back in an hour to check you again.", "answer": " thank you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 37, "asentId": 38}, {"question": " thank you.  well, i guess we have some time to kill.", "answer": " yeah, guess so. whew! check these out!  never done this before.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 39, "asentId": 40}, {"question": " thank you very much.", "answer": " thanks.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 43, "asentId": 44}, {"question": " hi! hi, i&#146;m uh ross. i&#146;m here to ruin this magical day for you.", "answer": " oh no-no, not at all.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 45, "asentId": 46}, {"question": " don&#146;t worry about it.", "answer": " marc coreger, this is my wife julie.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 47, "asentId": 48}, {"question": " hi julie.", "answer": " hi.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 49, "asentId": 50}, {"question": " hi!", "answer": " oh hi rachel.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 53, "asentId": 54}, {"question": " how are you?", "answer": " hi. is this your first?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 55, "asentId": 56}, {"question": " yeah it is.", "answer": " well, little jamie here is our third. so, if you have questions or you need anything at all, just holler.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 57, "asentId": 58}, {"question": " that&#146;s so sweet.", "answer": " yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 59, "asentId": 60}, {"question": " oh.", "answer": " umm say, i-i opened this earlier  but let me give you guys some privacy.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 61, "asentId": 62}, {"question": " no nonsense! we&#146;re all in this together.", "answer": " yeah, we are going to share every moment of this with you. and i think we&#146;re gonna have some fun.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 63, "asentId": 64}, {"question": " yeah.", "answer": " oh, okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 65, "asentId": 66}, {"question": " oh no, i really don&#146;t want any&#151;&#151;oh! thank you. oh. oh ross&#133;", "answer": " what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 69, "asentId": 70}, {"question": " here comes another contraction.", "answer": " oh. okay, just breathe.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 71, "asentId": 72}, {"question": "  oh wow, three hours and still no baby. ugh, the miracle of birth sure is a snooze fest.", "answer": " hey, you wanna see something?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 77, "asentId": 78}, {"question": " sure! what?", "answer": " umm, this is going to be fun. watch me freak out chandler. honey?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 79, "asentId": 80}, {"question": " yeah?", "answer": " listen uh, i-i&#146;ve been doing some thinking, and i don&#146;t know whether it&#146;s because we&#146;re here or rachel&#146;s giving birth but umm, i think we should try to have a baby.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 81, "asentId": 82}, {"question": " okay.", "answer": "  what-what-what&#146;s that now?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 83, "asentId": 84}, {"question": " okay. i&#146;ve been thinking about it too, and i, i think we&#146;re ready.", "answer": " what?! are you kidding me?! you-you-you think we&#146;re ready to have a baby now?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 85, "asentId": 86}, {"question": " oh, this is fun.", "answer": " you&#146;re ready to have a baby? my boy&#146;s all grown up!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 87, "asentId": 88}, {"question": " but you said you were ready too.", "answer": " yeah but i was just screwing with you to try to get your voice all high and weird like mine is now!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 89, "asentId": 90}, {"question": " yes, but haven&#146;t you wanted a kid like forever?", "answer": " okay, just back off mister! whoa.  &#145;cause i am ready to have a baby. i just want joey to be the father.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 91, "asentId": 92}, {"question": "  what?! are you crazy?!", "answer": " that&#146;s it! right there! is all i wanted!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 93, "asentId": 94}, {"question": " i am so sorry. the doctor insisted on closing the curtain for the exam.", "answer": " oh, that&#146;s very&#151;really very-very okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 95, "asentId": 96}, {"question": " julie&#146;s cervix is dilated a seven centimeters, that&#146;s about four fingers. the doctor let me feel it myself.", "answer": " have you felt rachel&#146;s cervix ross?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 97, "asentId": 98}, {"question": "  no, i don&#146;t think we&#146;ll be doing that.", "answer": "  we&#146;re not gonna do that.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 99, "asentId": 100}, {"question": " well, if you like you can feel rachel&#146;s and then feel mine to compare.", "answer": "  am i interrupting?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 101, "asentId": 102}, {"question": " uh yes! thank you.", "answer": " oh. oh wait no.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 103, "asentId": 104}, {"question": " later.", "answer": " no-no-don&#146;t! don&#146;t leave me here with these people.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 105, "asentId": 106}, {"question": " hi! i&#146;m so glad you&#146;re here, but it&#146;s gonna be a while. i-i wished you&#146;d called first.", "answer": " oh that&#146;s all right, i&#146;m coming back later with your father.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 111, "asentId": 112}, {"question": " oh good.", "answer": " i actually needed to talk to you before the birth.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 113, "asentId": 114}, {"question": " okay, what&#146;s up?", "answer": " i brought something that i want to give you, assuming of course that you want it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 115, "asentId": 116}, {"question": " ma, you&#146;re asking me to marry you?", "answer": " this is your grandmother&#146;s engagement ring, i want you to give it to rachel.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 117, "asentId": 118}, {"question": " mom no, come on! thank you.", "answer": " just hear me out!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 119, "asentId": 120}, {"question": " n-no! okay? we&#146;ve been through this! we&#146;re not gonna get married just because she&#146;s pregnant, okay?", "answer": " honestly! ross, this isn&#146;t just some girl you picked up in a bar and humped. a child should have a family.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 121, "asentId": 122}, {"question": " mom, y&#146;know what? i-i can&#146;t deal with this right now. i&#146;m sorry&#133;", "answer": " just&#133;think about it. if you don&#146;t, i&#146;ll talk more about humping.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 123, "asentId": 124}, {"question": " hi!", "answer": " oh hi dear!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 127, "asentId": 128}, {"question": " &#133;she came and dragged me out of the labor room to ask me why i&#146;m not with rachel.", "answer": " yeah.  why aren&#146;t you with rachel?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 131, "asentId": 132}, {"question": " are you kidding? look, we&#146;re not gonna be together just because we&#146;re having a baby. okay?", "answer": " but y&#146;know what? it just seems that you two belong together.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 133, "asentId": 134}, {"question": " okay, stop it! i can&#146;t deal with this right now. i have to go have a baby.", "answer": " right. and with who again?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 135, "asentId": 136}, {"question": " god. he&#146;s crazy! why doesn&#146;t he want to be with rachel?", "answer": " i know!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 137, "asentId": 138}, {"question": "  hey. who&#146;s that?", "answer": " new people.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 141, "asentId": 142}, {"question": " what happened to the disgustingtons?", "answer": " they&#146;re having their baby! it&#146;s not fair ross we got here first! right after you left they wheeled her off into delivery. oh but not before she gave me a juicy shot of little jamie just crowning away.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 143, "asentId": 144}, {"question": " wow! sorry. so uh, how are the new people?", "answer": " well they have uh, some unusual pet names for each other. including umm, evil bitch and uh, sick bastard. oh god oh! contraction!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 145, "asentId": 146}, {"question": " yeah? okay.", "answer": " ooh! ow!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 147, "asentId": 148}, {"question": " are you looking at her?!", "answer": " no!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 149, "asentId": 150}, {"question": " don&#146;t you look at her you sick bastard!", "answer": " honey i swear! i wasn&#146;t looking at her!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 151, "asentId": 152}, {"question": " she&#146;s in labor! you like that you sick son of a bitch!", "answer": " umm. umm, i&#146;m-i&#146;m just gonna&#151;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 153, "asentId": 154}, {"question": " see? see? it was because you were looking fat pervert!", "answer": " no-no, i&#146;m&#133;i&#146;m sure no one was looking. just want some privacy.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 155, "asentId": 156}, {"question": " you miss your girlfriend?", "answer": " just ignore them.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 157, "asentId": 158}, {"question": " ross.", "answer": " what? what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 159, "asentId": 160}, {"question": " he&#146;s looking at me.", "answer": "  hey! you wanna live to see your baby?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 161, "asentId": 162}, {"question": " what is going on with you? since when are you so crazy about babies?", "answer": " i&#146;m not crazy about babies. i&#146;m crazy about us.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 167, "asentId": 168}, {"question": " what?", "answer": " look, we&#146;ve always talked about having babies someday. i&#146;m not saying it has to be right now, but i&#146;m starting to think that we can handle it. we&#146;re good. we&#146;re really good.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 169, "asentId": 170}, {"question": " we are pretty good.", "answer": " but nothing has to happen until your ready.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 171, "asentId": 172}, {"question": " well maybe i&#146;m ready now. i mean, it&#146;s a little scary, but maybe it&#146;s right.", "answer": " what?! it&#146;s not right! we&#146;re not ready to have a kid now!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 173, "asentId": 174}, {"question": " what?!!", "answer": " i&#146;m kidding. this is going to be fun.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 175, "asentId": 176}, {"question": " so we&#146;re gonna try? i mean, are we trying?", "answer": " we&#146;re trying to get pregnant.  y&#146;know i&#146;m not really comfortable doing this in front of the babies. so, when do you want to start trying?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 177, "asentId": 178}, {"question": " okay, hold on a sec.", "answer": " period math?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 179, "asentId": 180}, {"question": " yeah.", "answer": " yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 181, "asentId": 182}, {"question": " well, we could start trying. now.", "answer": " right here?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 183, "asentId": 184}, {"question": " no, not here. maybe here.", "answer": " wait a minute, it&#146;s perfect. we got a lot of time to kill and we&#146;re in a building that&#146;s full of beds!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 185, "asentId": 186}, {"question": " come on you stupid machine! come on!", "answer": " oh, it ate your money?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 189, "asentId": 190}, {"question": "  no.", "answer": " all right, i&#146;ll see you downstairs then.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 191, "asentId": 192}, {"question": " all right.", "answer": " all right.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 193, "asentId": 194}, {"question": " hi!", "answer": " hi.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 197, "asentId": 198}, {"question": " oh uh, up or down?", "answer": " oh down please.  i-i hate to be a ball buster can i just do it?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 199, "asentId": 200}, {"question": " could you press up too please?", "answer": " sure! i feel so bad for you; i broke my leg once too.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 201, "asentId": 202}, {"question": " oh yeah? how&#146;d yours happen?", "answer": " well, it&#146;s a long story. it&#146;s kind of embarrassing. let&#146;s just say there was a typographical error with a sex manual.  how about you?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 203, "asentId": 204}, {"question": " car accident.", "answer": " oh.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 205, "asentId": 206}, {"question": " oh, let me guess some idiot on a cell phone wasn&#146;t paying attention?", "answer": " yeah. me.  oh hey, that&#146;s me.  hey uh, i take it you&#146;re just visiting someone.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 207, "asentId": 208}, {"question": " uh-huh, yeah.", "answer": " well umm, if you have sometime y&#146;know and maybe you might want to visit someone else&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 209, "asentId": 210}, {"question": " oh yeah! i-i would like that.", "answer": " i&#146;m in the middle&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 211, "asentId": 212}, {"question": " wait! what?! no!! elevator!! no!", "answer": "  uh, you gotta press the button.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 213, "asentId": 214}, {"question": " the nurse said they&#146;re bringing in another woman.", "answer": " ugh, is she pregnant yet? she doesn&#146;t need to be; she&#146;ll still have the baby before i do. oh ross, another contraction!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 215, "asentId": 216}, {"question": " oooh, that sounded like a bad one.", "answer": " yeah it was.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 219, "asentId": 220}, {"question": "  excuse me? could you help me with something? the patient i&#146;m looking for has a broken leg and is in a wheelchair. and umm, he&#146;s like early to mid-thirties, very attractive.", "answer": " i think i know who you&#146;re talking about.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 223, "asentId": 224}, {"question": " oh yay! great! okay, what room number is he in?", "answer": " i&#146;m sorry, that information is restricted to hospital staff&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 225, "asentId": 226}, {"question": "  uh, she&#146;s with me.  dr. drake remoray.", "answer": " dr. drake who?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 227, "asentId": 228}, {"question": " remoray. it&#146;s portuguese. we need that information; i&#146;m a doctor.", "answer": " a doctor at this hospital?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 229, "asentId": 230}, {"question": " damnit woman we&#146;re losing precious time! now do you want this man&#146;s blood on your head?", "answer": " hands.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 231, "asentId": 232}, {"question": " hands! it is absolutely essential that you tell me what room the man my assistant described is staying in. he&#146;s a patient of mine, i&#146;ve been treating him for years!", "answer": " he&#146;s in room 816.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 233, "asentId": 234}, {"question": " 816, thank you!", "answer": " thank you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 235, "asentId": 236}, {"question": " and what is his name?", "answer": "  no!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 237, "asentId": 238}, {"question": " i think we found a place.", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 239, "asentId": 240}, {"question": " umm, wait! do you want to set the mood a little?", "answer": " okay. uh, we&#146;ll dim the lights, dim the lights.  or turn them out all together. uh, no scented candles. okay here. here we go.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 241, "asentId": 242}, {"question": " ooh, this is it!  oh, that&#146;s him! that&#146;s him!", "answer": " great! go get him.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 249, "asentId": 250}, {"question": " wait a second, or maybe you can go in first.", "answer": "  he&#146;s not really my type.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 251, "asentId": 252}, {"question": " no not you, dr. drake remoray. you can ask him questions and see what&#146;s he like. people tell doctors everything.", "answer": " but you said he was this great guy!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 253, "asentId": 254}, {"question": " but lately all the guys i meet seem really nice at first, then they turn out to be the biggest jerks.", "answer": " you do attract some stinkers.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 255, "asentId": 256}, {"question": " dr. long, i&#146;ve been at this for seventeen hours! three women have come and gone with their babies, you gotta give me some good news! how many centimeters am i dilated? eight? nine?", "answer": " three.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 257, "asentId": 258}, {"question": " just three?! i&#146;m dilated three!", "answer": " we are moving along, just slowly.  don&#146;t worry, you&#146;re doing great. i&#146;ll be back soon.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 259, "asentId": 260}, {"question": " oh my. we&#146;re gonna need to take you straight to the delivery room.", "answer": " oh for the love of god! woman giving birth:  it&#146;s coming! it&#146;s coming!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 267, "asentId": 268}, {"question": " hi! i&#146;m dr. drake remoray and i have a few routine questions i need to ask you.", "answer": " really? i&#146;ve been dealing with dr. wells.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 273, "asentId": 274}, {"question": " i know, but i&#146;m a neurologist. and just to be on the safe side, dr. wells wanted a more comprehensive overview of you status so he sent me.", "answer": " dr. wells is a woman.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 275, "asentId": 276}, {"question": " that was a test. good response. all right, full name.", "answer": " clifford burnett.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 277, "asentId": 278}, {"question": " date of birth?", "answer": " november 16th, 1968.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 279, "asentId": 280}, {"question": " age?", "answer": " can&#146;t you figure that out based on my date of birth?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 281, "asentId": 282}, {"question": " i&#146;m a doctor cliff, not a mathematician.", "answer": " i&#146;m 33.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 283, "asentId": 284}, {"question": " okay. and uh, are you married.", "answer": " no.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 285, "asentId": 286}, {"question": " oh really? so, 33 and still single, would you say you have commitment issues?", "answer": " are all the questions this personal?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 287, "asentId": 288}, {"question": "  yes.", "answer": " well uh if you must know i&#146;m a widower.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 289, "asentId": 290}, {"question": " oh that&#146;s terrible. i&#146;m-i&#146;m really sorry.", "answer": " yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 291, "asentId": 292}, {"question": " hmm. do you sleep with women and never call them again?", "answer": " no.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 293, "asentId": 294}, {"question": " excellent! excellent! and uh, finally, are you into any weird stuff y&#146;know, sexually?", "answer": " no!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 295, "asentId": 296}, {"question": "  this room&#146;s available.", "answer": " okay! okay wait! you listen to me! you listen to me! since i have been waiting four women, that&#146;s four, one higher than the number of centimeters that i am dilated, have come and gone with their babies! i&#146;m next! it&#146;s my turn! it&#146;s only fair! and if you bring in one woman and she has her baby before me i&#146;m going to sue you! not this hospital, i&#146;m going to sue you! and my husband  he&#146;s a lawyer!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 299, "asentId": 300}, {"question": " uh rach&#133;", "answer": " go get back on that case honey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 301, "asentId": 302}, {"question": " i don&#146;t think the next patient is very far along.", "answer": " okay, well then bring her in.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 303, "asentId": 304}, {"question": " i&#133;.can&#146;t&#133;.believe this!", "answer": " and yet somehow it&#146;s true!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 307, "asentId": 308}, {"question": "  squeeze your legs together and cover the baby&#146;s ears!", "answer": "  hi sweetie!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 311, "asentId": 312}, {"question": " i still can&#146;t believe it! i&#146;m the luckiest guy in the world!", "answer": "  really?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 315, "asentId": 316}, {"question": "  what&#146;d he say?", "answer": " oh y&#146;know what? you have to speak very loudly when you&#146;re talking to sid, because he&#146;s almost completely deaf.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 317, "asentId": 318}, {"question": " oh!", "answer": " oh there you go!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 319, "asentId": 320}, {"question": " i get it!", "answer": " so? congratulations you two, i didn&#146;t even know you got married.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 321, "asentId": 322}, {"question": " oh we-we didn&#146;t.", "answer": " no-no. we&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 323, "asentId": 324}, {"question": " what?!", "answer": " um uh&#133;we&#146;re-we&#146;re just having this baby together but uh, uh that&#146;s all.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 325, "asentId": 326}, {"question": " why?!!", "answer": " uh well umm&#133;we&#146;re just not in that place, y&#146;know? but we&#146;re very excited about this.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 327, "asentId": 328}, {"question": " just tell me how.", "answer": " uh-oh, i feel another one coming.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 331, "asentId": 332}, {"question": " what else? what else?", "answer": " uh, well he&#146;s 33.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 335, "asentId": 336}, {"question": " oh. ah-uh.", "answer": " a widower.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 337, "asentId": 338}, {"question": " oh.", "answer": " he seemed like a stand up guy. oh, and he&#146;s not into anything weird sexually.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 339, "asentId": 340}, {"question": " should we tell rachel there&#146;s an empty private room right next door to hers?", "answer": " we could, or we can have sex in it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 343, "asentId": 344}, {"question": " does that sound like janice?", "answer": " if it&#146;s not, then there&#146;s two of them. and that would mean it&#146;s the end of the world!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 349, "asentId": 350}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": " hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 351, "asentId": 352}, {"question": " hi.", "answer": " oh hi.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 353, "asentId": 354}, {"question": " i can&#146;t believe this is taking so long. how are you doing?", "answer": " oh not bad. do you know that feeling when you&#146;re trying to blow a saint bernard out your ass?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 355, "asentId": 356}, {"question": " weirdest thing. did i hear&#151;&#151;mother of god it&#146;s true!", "answer": " chandler bing!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 357, "asentId": 358}, {"question": " jan-janice!", "answer": " not just janice, janice in labor, contracting and everything.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 359, "asentId": 360}, {"question": " oh, this should be easy. i have a very wide pelvis. you remember chandler.", "answer": " janice i didn&#146;t even know you were pregnant! who&#146;s the unwitting human who&#146;s essence you&#146;ve stolen?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 361, "asentId": 362}, {"question": " it&#146;s you. this is yours.", "answer": " what?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 363, "asentId": 364}, {"question": " okay i&#146;ve got one for you, if you had too which one would you rather eat, a seeing eye dog or a talking gorilla?", "answer": " i&#146;d have to say&#133;the talking gorilla, because at least i can explain to him that you&#146;re making me eat him.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 369, "asentId": 370}, {"question": " no, i&#146;m sorry. it&#146;s just my foot itches like crazy.", "answer": " oh, i&#146;ll get it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 373, "asentId": 374}, {"question": " wow! i usually get to know a girl a little better before i let her spoon", "answer": " relax, it&#146;s not like we&#146;re forking.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 375, "asentId": 376}, {"question": " oh that&#146;s five ross. five women have had five babies! and i have had no babies! why doesn&#146;t she want to come out?", "answer": " y&#146;know what i think it is? i think you&#146;ve made such a nice home for her over the last nine months that she just doesn&#146;t want to leave.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 377, "asentId": 378}, {"question": " twenty-one hours, you&#146;re a hero.", "answer": " doctor you gotta do something! i think you gotta give me drugs or you gotta light a fire up in there and just smoke it out.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 381, "asentId": 382}, {"question": " actually, i think you&#146;re ready to go to the delivery room.", "answer": " what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 383, "asentId": 384}, {"question": " ten centimeters, you&#146;re about to become a mom.", "answer": " my god. okay.  ha-ha-ha beat ya! sucker!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 385, "asentId": 386}, {"question": " oh my god! that&#146;s the doctor who was in my room before!", "answer": " huh. okay, mr. perkazet.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 391, "asentId": 392}, {"question": " i&#146;m telling you! the guy from that show was here in my room, asking me all these weird questions!", "answer": " cliff, do you really believe that a character from a tv show was here in your room?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 393, "asentId": 394}, {"question": "  rachel&#146;s having her baby!!  which is of no interest to me, i&#146;m a neurologist.", "answer": " that-that&#146;s him! you know him?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 395, "asentId": 396}, {"question": " okay. okay. i&#151;okay umm&#133;this&#133;i-i sent my friend joey in here to find out stuff about you. umm y&#146;know, if it helps you came off great. a lot better than i&#146;m coming off right now.", "answer": " i don&#146;t believe this. you got him to pretend he was some fake doctor?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 397, "asentId": 398}, {"question": " and then you tried to make me think that i was crazy.", "answer": " you&#146;re right, that was wrong. i&#146;m sorry. i&#146;m so sorry. it&#146;s just that i liked you so much. can we just, can we just start over?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 401, "asentId": 402}, {"question": " i don&#146;t think so.", "answer": " uh, if i may? umm-umm look, cliff, you told me a lot of personal stuff about you, right? and maybe-maybe it would if-if would help if-if you knew some personal stuff about her. uh, she was married to a gay ice dancer. uh, she gave birth to her brother&#146;s triplets. oh! oh! her-her twin sister used to do porn!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 403, "asentId": 404}, {"question": " uh joey, we&#146;re trying to dial down the crazy.", "answer": " right!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 405, "asentId": 406}, {"question": " umm, look we don&#146;t, we don&#146;t really know each other so it would be really easy to just forget about this, but there seems to be something between us. and i don&#146;t know about you but that doesn&#146;t happen to me a lot.", "answer": " it doesn&#146;t happen to me either.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 407, "asentId": 408}, {"question": " push. push. come on push for five seconds. 5&#133;4&#133;", "answer": " 3-2-1 oh!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 411, "asentId": 412}, {"question": " okay, the next contraction should be in about twenty seconds.", "answer": " i can&#146;t. i can&#146;t push anymore, i can&#146;t.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 413, "asentId": 414}, {"question": " sweetie you&#146;re doing great.", "answer": " oh god twenty seconds my ass!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 415, "asentId": 416}, {"question": " here we go! okay, keep pushing! wait! i see something.", "answer": " what? you do? you do?  oh my god!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 417, "asentId": 418}, {"question": " don&#146;t say, &quot;oh my god!&quot; oh my god what?", "answer": " what is that?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 419, "asentId": 420}, {"question": " it&#146;s the baby&#146;s buttock, she&#146;s breech.", "answer": " oh thank god, i thought she had two heads.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 421, "asentId": 422}, {"question": " oh god. is she gonna be okay?", "answer": " she&#146;s gonna be fine. okay, she&#146;s in a more difficult position so you&#146;re gonna have to push even harder now. go! push!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 423, "asentId": 424}, {"question": " go!", "answer": " rachel you&#146;re gonna have to push even harder, nothing&#146;s happening!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 425, "asentId": 426}, {"question": " i&#146;m sorry, i can&#146;t!", "answer": " yes you can!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 427, "asentId": 428}, {"question": " i can&#146;t!", "answer": " hey! hey! come on! you can! i know you can do this! let&#146;s go!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 429, "asentId": 430}, {"question": " i can&#146;t. please, you do it for me.", "answer": " no! come on let&#146;s&#151;one more time! one final push! ready? 1&#133;2&#133;3!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 431, "asentId": 432}, {"question": " good!", "answer": "  keep pushing!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 433, "asentId": 434}, {"question": " are you okay?", "answer": " you have no idea how much this hurts.  keep going! keep going!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 435, "asentId": 436}, {"question": " here we go!", "answer": " oh! oh! she&#146;s upside down but she&#146;s coming! she&#146;s coming!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 437, "asentId": 438}, {"question": " oh god!", "answer": " oh! oh my god oh! oh my god she&#146;s here.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 439, "asentId": 440}, {"question": " oh she&#146;s&#133;she&#146;s perfect.", "answer": " oh, she&#146;s so tiny.  where&#146;d she go?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 441, "asentId": 442}, {"question": " oh it&#146;s okay. they&#146;re just-they&#146;re just wrapping her up.", "answer": " okay. well be careful with her, she&#146;s really tiny.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 443, "asentId": 444}, {"question": " oh hey you. thanks for coming out of me.  i know. oh. yeah. oh, she&#146;s looking at me. hi! i know you.", "answer": " do we have a name yet?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 447, "asentId": 448}, {"question": " no, not yet.", "answer": " that&#146;s fine, for now we&#146;ll just call her baby girl green.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 449, "asentId": 450}, {"question": " can we come in?", "answer": " oh, come in.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 455, "asentId": 456}, {"question": " hi!", "answer": " there she is!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 457, "asentId": 458}, {"question": " oh, she&#146;s so beautiful.", "answer": " here.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 459, "asentId": 460}, {"question": " oh my god! she&#146;s amazing. oh, oh i&#146;m so glad you guys got drunk and had sex!", "answer": " it&#146;s incredible, i mean one minute she&#146;s inside you and then 47 hours later here she is.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 461, "asentId": 462}, {"question": "  she looks so real!  y&#146;know what i mean! she&#146;s this whole tiny little person. she already has eyelashes and knees and&#133;uh-oh.", "answer": " what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 463, "asentId": 464}, {"question": " oh no-no, no for i second there i counted six fingers, but one was from the other hand so we&#146;re good.", "answer": " okay, my turn. my turn.  oh! you&#146;re so cute! oh, i could squeeze your little head!  i won&#146;t.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 465, "asentId": 466}, {"question": " what&#146;s the matter?", "answer": " oh nothing i&#133; sorry, i just can&#146;t stop crying.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 467, "asentId": 468}, {"question": " the doctor says it&#146;s completely normal with all the hormones. plus, you-you&#146;re sleep deprived.", "answer": " so? you guys are all sleep deprived. i don&#146;t see you weeping because you put your slippers on the wrong feet. oh god.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 469, "asentId": 470}, {"question": " what&#146;s the matter now?", "answer": " i was reliving it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 471, "asentId": 472}, {"question": " so, do you know what you&#146;re gonna call her yet?", "answer": " oh, wait a minute it&#146;s not gonna be baby girl? i thought that was so original!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 475, "asentId": 476}, {"question": " uh actually, we-we&#146;ve narrowed it down to two names.", "answer": " yeah, and y&#146;know what? i love them both, so why don&#146;t you just pick one and that&#146;ll be it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 477, "asentId": 478}, {"question": " wow! umm, okay uh&#133;everyone&#133;this&#133;is isabella.  what?", "answer": " that&#146;s not her name! i&#146;m sorry, she just doesn&#146;t feel like an isabella.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 479, "asentId": 480}, {"question": " so then i guess ferdinad is out.", "answer": " what was the other one ross?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 481, "asentId": 482}, {"question": " umm, delilah.", "answer": " oh great! suddenly she sounds like a biblical whore.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 483, "asentId": 484}, {"question": " so i guess we&#146;re back to uh, baby girl.", "answer": " yay!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 485, "asentId": 486}, {"question": " well what are we going to do?", "answer": " it&#146;s okay honey, you&#146;ll find a name.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 487, "asentId": 488}, {"question": " ugh, easy for you to say, you already know what your kids names are going to be.", "answer": " you do?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 489, "asentId": 490}, {"question": " yeah, i&#146;ve had them picked out since i was fourteen.", "answer": " oh no, it&#146;s gonna be named after some snack or baked good isn&#146;t it?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 491, "asentId": 492}, {"question": " well tell us! what are they?", "answer": " umm, okay. if it&#146;s a boy it&#146;s daniel.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 493, "asentId": 494}, {"question": " and if it&#146;s a girl?", "answer": " i don&#146;t want to say.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 495, "asentId": 496}, {"question": " oh, just tell us! we&#146;re not gonna want it!", "answer": " okay. it&#146;s emma.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 497, "asentId": 498}, {"question": "  emma!  see? i don&#146;t want it.", "answer": " take it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 499, "asentId": 500}, {"question": " what?", "answer": " it&#146;s clearly an emma.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 501, "asentId": 502}, {"question": " oh honey, but you love that name.", "answer": " yeah, but i love you more. besides y&#146;know, nothing goes with bing. so i&#146;m screwed. i mean&#133;  oh, hi emma. yeah, that&#146;s you. you&#146;re our little em. oh what&#146;s that honey? what? oh, you want a little cousin?  you want a cousin right now?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 503, "asentId": 504}, {"question": " that was amazing.", "answer": " i know. hey, do you realize we may have just changed our lives forever? we may have just started a family. nine months from now we can be here, having our own baby.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 505, "asentId": 506}, {"question": "  yoo-hoo! aaron litman-neurolic would like to say hello to his future bride.", "answer": " ohhh!  wow! he kinda takes your breath away doesn&#146;t he?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 509, "asentId": 510}, {"question": " he&#146;s a keeper. how are you feeling?", "answer": " oh, i&#146;m fine.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 511, "asentId": 512}, {"question": " can i just say, i really admire what you&#146;re doing. just raising her all alone.", "answer": " oh, i&#146;m not doing it alone. i have ross.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 513, "asentId": 514}, {"question": " oh, sure. now. but what happens when he meets somebody else and gets married?", "answer": " well then he gets a divorce, it&#146;s ross!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 515, "asentId": 516}, {"question": " i&#146;m telling you rachel, listen to janice. they all say they&#146;re gonna be there until they start their real family.", "answer": " well i&#151;that&#146;s never gonna happen with ross.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 517, "asentId": 518}, {"question": " oh well that&#146;s what i thought about my first husband, now i&#146;m lucky if my kid gets to spend the weekend with her father and the twins and little ms. new boobs.", "answer": " really?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 519, "asentId": 520}, {"question": " i hate to be the one to say it, but honey you two  are on your own.", "answer": " well&#133; that&#146;s&#133;y&#146;know&#151;that&#146;s&#151;we&#146;ve been alone for the last twenty minutes we&#146;re doing okay. besides y&#146;know what? i-i&#151;maybe we won&#146;t be alone, &#145;cause lately i-i&#151;things have been happening between me and ross, y&#146;know? right before i went into labor, we-we had this kiss. y&#146;know? so it might be the&#133;the beginning of something.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 521, "asentId": 522}, {"question": "  hey janice!", "answer": " oh hi!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 523, "asentId": 524}, {"question": " say hello to aaron, your future son-in-law.", "answer": " no-no. no.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 527, "asentId": 528}, {"question": " i&#146;m gonna leave the three of you alone.", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 529, "asentId": 530}, {"question": " man! did you see the kid on that nose?", "answer": " uh-huh.  y&#146;know what i was, i was thinking about?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 533, "asentId": 534}, {"question": " huh?", "answer": " umm&#133;that kiss before we left the apartment. that was some-something huh?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 535, "asentId": 536}, {"question": " yeah. yeah, it really was. but we&#133;we gotta be careful. we&#133;we can&#146;t let that happen again, y&#146;know?", "answer": "  right.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 537, "asentId": 538}, {"question": " i mean we don&#146;t want to go down that road do we?", "answer": " no! no, of course not. no. that&#146;s why i brought it up.  they didn&#146;t have any sodas?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 539, "asentId": 540}, {"question": " oh my god! i&#146;m sorry, i was talking to this nurse, completely forgot.", "answer": " that&#146;s all right.  and so it begins.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 541, "asentId": 542}, {"question": " is she in there?", "answer": " yeah. she&#146;s putting her down now, that&#146;s her.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 543, "asentId": 544}, {"question": " oh!", "answer": " look at emma!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 545, "asentId": 546}, {"question": " i just can&#146;t decide who she looks more alike, you or rachel?", "answer": " oh what are you kidding? she&#146;s gorgeous, it&#146;s all rachel.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 547, "asentId": 548}, {"question": " i&#146;m sorry, for the last time, why aren&#146;t you two together again?  no, i know. i know, because you&#146;re not in that place. which would be fine, except you totally are.", "answer": " it&#146;s&#133;it&#146;s complicated okay?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 549, "asentId": 550}, {"question": " yeah that&#146;s true. yeah, you love her. you always have. you have a child together. there is no right answer.", "answer": " look, we&#146;ve been together. okay? and then apart, and then together, and then apart, and now we have a baby.  it&#146;s just if-if we got together again and it didn&#146;t work out&#133;i could never do that to emma. i mean she-she thinking everything&#151; oh that&#146;s&#133;now me. what do they put something in the water in this place? since rachel and i we&#146;re doing really, we&#146;re doing really well right now.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 551, "asentId": 552}, {"question": " i know. i know. i know. i know, and if you try to make it more you might wreck it.", "answer": " yeah, exactly.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 553, "asentId": 554}, {"question": " hey. i just saw a woman breast feeding both of her twins at the same time; it is like a freak show up here.  what&#146;s the matter?", "answer": " nothing.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 557, "asentId": 558}, {"question": " what is it? hey!", "answer": " really it&#146;s nothing. i&#146;m just&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 559, "asentId": 560}, {"question": " rach come on, what?", "answer": " i&#146;ve just been thinking about how my baby and i are gonna be all alone.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 561, "asentId": 562}, {"question": " what are you talking about alone? what about ross?", "answer": " oh please, he&#146;ll be with his real family, the twins and little miss new boobs.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 563, "asentId": 564}, {"question": " okay, how long was i watching that woman?", "answer": " i&#146;m just saying that y&#146;know, someday ross is gonna meet somebody and&#133;he&#146;s gonna have his own life. right?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 565, "asentId": 566}, {"question": " yeah, i guess so.", "answer": " i just never thought i would raise this baby all by myself. pretty dumb huh?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 567, "asentId": 568}, {"question": " hey, listen to me, listen to me&#133;you are never ever gonna be alone. okay? i promise that&#146;s not gonna happen.", "answer": " joey. honey what would i do without you?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 569, "asentId": 570}, {"question": " oh, hon can you grab me my other box of tissues? they&#146;re right on that chair under ross&#146;s coat.", "answer": " sure.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 573, "asentId": 574}, {"question": " my god.", "answer": " joey.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 577, "asentId": 578}]